const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Rods are concentrated in which of the following regions?","answers":[{"option":"Nissels Granules","bool":false},{"option":"Parafoveal region","bool":true},{"option":"Synaptic bulb","bool":false},{"option":"Maculae","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"The auditory tube is found in which of the following walls of middle ear cavity?","answers":[{"option":"Anterior wall","bool":true},{"option":"Roof","bool":false},{"option":"Floor","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral wall","bool":false},{"option":"Medial wall","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following nerves supplies the nasopharynx?","answers":[{"option":"Maxillary nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Ophthalmic nerve","bool":false},{"option":"All of them","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"A girl wearing tops suffers an infection. Which of the following lymph nodes would be involved?","answers":[{"option":"Maxillary nodes","bool":false},{"option":"Deep cervical nodes","bool":false},{"option":"Axillary nodes","bool":false},{"option":"Mastoid nodes","bool":false},{"option":"Superficial cervical nodes","bool":true}]},{"id":4,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Third-order neurons of the olfactory bulb terminate into which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Hypothalamus","bool":false},{"option":"Frontal lobe","bool":false},{"option":"Basal ganglia","bool":false},{"option":"Temporal lobe","bool":true},{"option":"Thalamus","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"In which of the following structures does the nasolacrimal duct open into?","answers":[{"option":"Middle meatus","bool":false},{"option":"Superior meatus","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior meatus","bool":true},{"option":"Infraorbital foramen","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following is not a derivative of 2nd pharyngeal arch?","answers":[{"option":"Stylohyoid","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Stapedius","bool":false},{"option":"Levator veli palatini","bool":true},{"option":"Buccinator","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Posterior 1/3rd of the tongue is supplied by which nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Olfactory nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Trigeminal nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"The pterygoid venous plexus drains into which of the following structures?","answers":[{"option":"Maxillary vein","bool":true},{"option":"External jugular vein","bool":false},{"option":"Middle meningeal vein","bool":false},{"option":"Facial vein","bool":false},{"option":"Cavernous sinus","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following ways is used to calculate intelligence quotient (IQ)?","answers":[{"option":"Dividing mental age by chronological age","bool":true},{"option":"Multiplying mental age with chronological age","bool":false},{"option":"Subtracting chronological age from mental age","bool":false},{"option":"Dividing chronological age by mental age","bool":false},{"option":"Subtracting mental age from chronological age","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following structures is formed by the union of the retromandibular vein and posterior auricular vein?","answers":[{"option":"External jugular vein","bool":true},{"option":"Superficial temporal vein","bool":false},{"option":"Subclavian vein","bool":false},{"option":"Common facial vein","bool":false},{"option":"Maxillary vein","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following is not a branch of facial artery?","answers":[{"option":"Superior labial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Submental artery","bool":false},{"option":"Transverse facial artery","bool":true},{"option":"Inferior labial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral nasal artery","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following structures passes through the parotid gland?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Internal carotid artery","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Internal jugular vein","bool":false},{"option":"Facial vein","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"When is the upper lip and palate formed?","answers":[{"option":"3rd-4th weeks of pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"21st-23rd weeks of pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"4th-5th weeks of pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"6th-9th weeks of pregnancy","bool":true},{"option":"13th-18th weeks of pregnancy","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following structures divides the parotid gland into superficial and deep parts?","answers":[{"option":"Retromandibular vein","bool":false},{"option":"Facial vein","bool":false},{"option":"Facial artery","bool":false},{"option":"External carotid artery","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":true}]},{"id":15,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"What is the collective name given to all refractive errors in both eyes?","answers":[{"option":"Anisometropia","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Amblyopia","bool":false},{"option":"Astigmatism","bool":false},{"option":"Ametropia","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following is the most common benign tumor of parotid gland?","answers":[{"option":"Acinic cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Myoepithelioma","bool":false},{"option":"Pleomorphic adenoma","bool":true},{"option":"Canalicular adenoma","bool":false},{"option":"Basal cell adenoma","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"The nerve supplying the muscles of mastication exits the skull through which of the following foramens?","answers":[{"option":"Foramen ovale","bool":true},{"option":"Mental foramen","bool":false},{"option":"Foramen spinosum","bool":false},{"option":"Foramen rotundum","bool":false},{"option":"Foramen lacerum","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following is not true regarding trochlear nerve?","answers":[{"option":"It passes through the cavernous sinus","bool":false},{"option":"Lesion results in upward deviation and lateral rotation","bool":true},{"option":"It supplies superior oblique","bool":false},{"option":"It supplies extraocular muscles","bool":false},{"option":"It is the only nerve arising from the back of brain stem","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"The scalp terminates at which of the following layers?","answers":[{"option":"Skin","bool":false},{"option":"Aponeurosis","bool":false},{"option":"Epicranium","bool":false},{"option":"Connective tissue","bool":false},{"option":"Pericranium","bool":true}]},{"id":20,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following antibodies is released by the parotid gland?","answers":[{"option":"IgM","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"IgD","bool":false},{"option":"IgA","bool":true},{"option":"IgE","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which nerve innervates the tip of the tongue?","answers":[{"option":"Abducens nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Mandibular nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Glossopharyngeal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Vagus nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following tongue papillae contain the greatest number of taste buds?","answers":[{"option":"Fungiform papillae","bool":false},{"option":"Circumvallate papillae","bool":true},{"option":"Filiform papillae","bool":false},{"option":"Foliate papillae","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following ions moves from endolymph to stereocilia to depolarize the hair cells?","answers":[{"option":"Na+","bool":false},{"option":"K+","bool":true},{"option":"Mg2+","bool":false},{"option":"Ca2+","bool":false},{"option":"Cl-","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"By the fifth week of pregnancy, six auricular hillocks appear on the face. These are the primordia of which of the following structures?","answers":[{"option":"Eyes","bool":false},{"option":"Internal ear","bool":false},{"option":"Tongue","bool":false},{"option":"External ear","bool":true},{"option":"Nose","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following boundaries of stomodeum are formed by maxillary prominences?","answers":[{"option":"Rostral","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Caudal","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Damage to which of the following muscles results in an inability to move the chin to the opposite side?","answers":[{"option":"Masseter","bool":false},{"option":"Buccinator","bool":false},{"option":"Levator scapulae","bool":false},{"option":"Temporalis","bool":false},{"option":"Sternocleidomastoid","bool":true}]},{"id":27,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following structures are not present in posterior triangle of neck?","answers":[{"option":"Supraclavicular lymph nodes","bool":true},{"option":"Trunks of brachial plexus","bool":false},{"option":"Cervical plexus","bool":false},{"option":"Subclavian artery","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following statements is true regarding Stenson's duct?","answers":[{"option":"It is a duct of the submandibular gland","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"It is a duct of the sublingual gland","bool":false},{"option":"It pierces the buccinator muscle","bool":true},{"option":"It arises from posterior surface of parotid gland","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"In cephalohematoma, fluid is present between which of the following structures?","answers":[{"option":"Dura and arachnoid","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Dural folds","bool":false},{"option":"Skull and periosteum","bool":true},{"option":"Arachnoid and pia","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Right homonymous hemianopia cannot be possible with lesion of which of the following structures?","answers":[{"option":"Visual cortex","bool":false},{"option":"Optic chiasm","bool":true},{"option":"Optic tract","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Optic radiation","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"An infarct of which of the following arteries will result in homonymous hemianopia?","answers":[{"option":"Anterior cerebral artery","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Middle cerebral artery","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior cerebral artery","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is responsible for opening of mouth?","answers":[{"option":"Lateral pterygoid","bool":true},{"option":"Temporalis","bool":false},{"option":"Masseter","bool":false},{"option":"Medial pterygoid","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"What is the principle of Rinne's test?","answers":[{"option":"Bone conduction is better than air conduction","bool":false},{"option":"Air conduction is the same as bone conduction","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Air conduction is better than bone conduction","bool":true},{"option":"All of these","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Lateralization to left ear can indicate which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Sensorineural hearing loss in left ear","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Sensorineural hearing loss in right ear","bool":true},{"option":"Conductive hearing loss in right ear","bool":false},{"option":"Combined hearing loss in left ear","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Which of the following are most likely to affect an individual’s personality?","answers":[{"option":"Gender","bool":false},{"option":"Health","bool":false},{"option":"Physical capabilities","bool":false},{"option":"Temperament","bool":true},{"option":"Skin color","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"2nd-year/head-and-neck/2016","question":"Correction of cleft lip usually occurs during which month?","answers":[{"option":"10th month","bool":false},{"option":"3rd month","bool":true},{"option":"9th month","bool":false},{"option":"6th month","bool":false},{"option":"12th month","bool":false}]}]
export default arr